Downloaded @ subs4free.club
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
I'm done.
I'll have the proofs from
the Ali-Frazier fight by 6:00.
Make it 4:00. Everybody out.
Serial killers, fruit loops,
lies and Jesus.
That's what
sells magazines, Bob.
You should lose all those
corny war photos out there.
What have you got for me?
I don't have time for
a cocktail-hour sip and grin.
I want you to speak at
the opening of my exhibition.
I just want you to say something
about how great I was.
- Uh... was?
- Yeah, how great I was.
I mean, how great I still am,
of course.
But, you know, way back then
when you could be great,
when the truth
still meant something.
So, yeah, you just have to say
that I'm the
greatest photographer
that 'LIFE' magazine
has ever had.
But you aren't.
You're the single most
impossible photographer
that 'LIFE' has ever had.
Well, fuck it.
Just say that, then.
I can't, Gene,
I told you when you called,
I'm out of town that week,
I've got a board meeting.
Look, Bob, I'm done. I'm tired.
My body's older than I am.
I'm always in goddamn pain.
I can't trust my fucking dick
anymore.
Constantly in a foul mood.
Even the fucking drugs bore me.
My kids won't speak to me.
You know...
I could go head first
into a fucking shrimp cocktail
at any given moment.
And I'm broke.
I'm sorry, Gene.
I wasn't looking
for your sympathy.
I was just stating the facts.
By the way, if anyone should be
asking for sympathy, Bob,
it should be you.
Look at this dreck
you're churning out.
Amazing.
No ladder and you got all
the way up on your high horse,
just like that.
We practically give this
magazine away to our readers.
We cover all the major issues
that touch their lives,
issues from all over the
country, all around the world.
We do it every week.
On top of that,
we fight television sets
for the same eyeballs
you took for granted
would always be there.
It gets worse. All the time.
What we do, what I do every day,
is find a way
to pay for all of this
and keep it going.
What we put on the cover,
what we put in the middle
of those stories,
that's what does that.
Wow.
Well, your horse is obviously
much higher than mine.
Consider this
as an overdue thankyou.
A royalty cheque you found
in an old pair of corduroys.
Cash it at the branch
on 17th and 6th.
Keep it off the books that way.
You know that you're only
sitting behind that desk
because of dogs like me, right?
Good luck, Gene. Don't waste
what time you got left.
You're a dick, Bob.
The date is Sunday,
February 28th, 1971.
Well, it's me. I've done it.
I've done the retrospective
and now I don't have to do
any more things.
Ahhh.
I sold all my stuff, you know,
my equipment, what have you,
and I'm gonna make sure
that you guys get the money
for that, 'cause, uh...
And, you know,
I hate to sound maudlin,
but, um...
..I think it's time for me to...
Goddamnit.
I'm coming!
- Mr Smith.
- Now's not the time.
Hi, I'm Aileen.
And this is our photographer,
Giichi.
Thanks. Thank you.
Wh-why is this man
giving me cookies?
Fuji Film.
We are here
for the advertisement.
Oh, that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, right, Christ.
Well, look, um, I'm gonna
have to level with you.
I have consumed quite a whole
lot of alcohol and I...
What did he say?
Giichi says you are
his favourite photographer
and the reason
he's gotten into the field.
Well, that's very nice.
That's very nice.
And... and... and...
what about you?
Have you never heard of me?
Not before this morning, no.
So you're not a fan?
It's too early to say.
Alright.
What do you want me to do?
They want you to say that
Fuji colour film is more vibrant
than any other colour film
on the markets.
It's the only colour film
you trust.
Turn that shit off.
Turn everything off. Um...
Do they really want me
to say that?
Yes. It was part of the deal.
Wow. Holy cow. Oh, fuck.
You know,
I've never shot in colour.
Ever. Not once. Never ever.
And anyone who knows my work
will know that.
So that's a very big problem.
I'm sorry,
but it's in the contract.
Did I sign the contract?
Will Naughton is playing
at Francesco's tonight.
Join me.
Alright.
Then let's get on with
the puppet show.
So, are you going to give me
a photography lesson?
Oh, listen, I would,
but I've... I've... I've damn near
sold off all my, uh, equipment.
I need to send money to my kids,
rent's way overdue,
and, uh, my bank account
just walked under a duck.
- So...
- What duck?
Oh, not a...
Not... not a real duck.
Never mind.
Sometimes you just get...
fed up with it.
You know, sometimes.
I used to be more fun.
I used to be a lot more fun.
I swear to you.
I bet you were a fun dad
to have five kids.
No. No, I wasn't.
Not even close.
I was never there.
I was gone all the time.
Absent.
No Little League.
No Barbies, no Easy-Bake Ovens.
I missed it all.
I had a great time
with you tonight, Aileen.
I...
..didn't just happen
to get this job with you.
Uh-huh.
There's a company in Japan...
..that's been dumping
their toxic waste
into the sea for years.
The Chisso Corporation.
People are getting sick
and dying.
The people need help.
There's a resistance
on the ground,
but we need global attention.
We need you at the shareholders
meeting next week.
Oh, well,
I'm afraid that Japan has seen
the last of me, kid.
That was 25 years ago.
Listen,
if that's why you're here,
I'll put you on a long list of
people that I've disappointed.
I'm terribly sorry.
Look, I've got a few things
to do, you know.
Defenestration and whatnot,
you know, so...
Sorry, I did that all wrong
and I've upset you.
It wasn't my intention.
No, no, it was a lovely night.
It was.
Hmm.
Yeah.
Here's some information.
Please have a look.
My number is on the envelope.
Take care, Aileen.
I love the, uh...
the suggestion for the centre.
It looks really...
It looks ideal to me.
This centre
is very strong.
- Yeah, um...
- Robert.
Good.
Robert, huge crisis in Japan.
Mercury poisoning.
There's your Pulitzer Prize.
- Gene, what the hell?!
- People are dying, Robert.
Yeah, all day, every day.
Doesn't mean you get to
fuck up my layout!
Oh, goddamnit.
Am I interrupting
your little layout?
Now, you guys just go on
and make room for your
fucking Oil of Olay ads
while innocent people drop
like flies, huh, Bob?
You're talking about Minamata.
Yeah.
See, she knows. She's smart.
Is there anybody else here
as smart as her?
A factory there's contaminating
the bay of some fishing village.
See?
First, they called it
'The Strange Disease',
then 'Dancing Cat Fever'
and now it's simply called
Minamata disease.
It's fucking monstrous.
I've been following it
in the 'Herald' and 'The Times'.
Small stories
every couple of months.
But no-one has
really covered it.
I mean,
it's in the goddamn fish.
And that's all those poor people
have to eat.
'The Times' has a Tokyo desk.
And we have deadlines
literally in one hour.
So that sounds to me, Bob,
like, uh, yeah,
time is of the essence.
And you know that the cover-up
is gonna be as much of a story
as the story itself.
I gotta go. Come on.
You expect me to send you?
You'd be a real dumbass not to.
Gene, stop.
A moment, if you please.
This is the story, Bob.
You know this is the story.
- I'm not sending you.
- What? Why not?
Gene, I'm gonna throw you out
of the goddamn window.
I wish you would've done that
last time I was here.
Gene, listen closely.
If I don't send you,
you can't fuck me on this,
you understand what I'm saying?
No.
Call me at home.
Don't call me here.
And you can't disappear
on me again.
Bob...
..I would never
disappoint you again.
Just try not to
disappoint yourself.
Gene, let's go!
I'm coming!
Hello.
Take off your shoes...
Take off your shoes.
- Excuse me.
- Thank you.
Listen! Children are asleep.
So, let's be quiet.
Ahh. You must be quiet.
The children are sleeping.
Oh. OK.
- Uh. Ah.
- Mmm.
Thank you very much.
This is not much.
- Please, have some food.
- Thank you very much.
Honestly, I don't really have so
much of an appetite right now.
But it's... it's definitely
coming back.
This food is...
I'd... I'd like...
I'm interested...
What? I'm interested in this.
Try this one.
Mmm!
- Very good?
- Mmm. Mmm!
It is good, isn't it?
- Is it good?
- Mm-hm. Mmm. Mmm.
- It is good.
- Very good.
- Hmm.
Mmm.
Well...
Actually...
It is hard to talk about those things.
It is not just about us.
It's not easy to speak
about certain things.
Akiko is our oldest.
They tried to tell us
it was cerebral palsy,
but we knew better.
She was born very sick
and she remains sick.
And she will never get better.
We are strong family.
She is our treasure.
We have six children,
and we all work hard
to take care of Akiko.
It takes five hours a day to feed her,
but she brings us closer as a family.
When you meet her, you'll see.
She is a beautiful soul.
We don't want to bring attention
to our family...
but we don't have a choice.
I drive a truck for Chisso.
For Chisso!
But it's not enough to take care
of a family with the needs we have.
- I will translate you later.
- Oh. Oh.
Can you, uh...
Can you please thank them
for their kindness,
their... their generosity
and for their hospitality?
And if... if it's
at all possible...
..to... photograph Akiko,
perhaps tomorrow.
Hmm.
- We thank you for your kindness.
- Ah, ah. Not at all.
If you don't mind...
Can we take some photos
of Akiko tomorrow?
Well really, that kind of thing...
...you'll have to excuse us
I'm sorry. No.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
- She will make our bed.
- Hmm. OK.
- Please! There's nothing much left but...
- Thank you.
Oh.
Oh, Aileen?
Would you mind asking if he
might have just a little...
..you know, sloop?
Yeah. Ahh.
Excuse me! Excuse me!
He seems that he cannot fall asleep.
Oh!
Do you have anything to drink?
A drink?
Just one minute.
He's got some?
- He loves whiskey for sure.
- Probably.
Whisky.
- Whisky.
- Oh. Good.
Whisky. Whisky.
- Good.
- Good whisky.
- Good night.
Ohh. Oh.
Many are tired of fighting
or they don't want to bring
attention to themselves.
Then there's us,
the Direct Negotiations Group.
We are not so easy
to keep quiet.
I can imagine.
Kiyoshi is one of
the lead activists
for the Direct
Negotiations Group.
Here. I got a light.
I got a light.
His son was born
with the disease.
Kiyoshi also has it,
but it's yet to be
officially recognised.
Alright? Got it?
- Thank you.
- For sure.
It's in my hands
and in... in my vision.
But it's my son and those
like him that keep me going.
Keep me fighting, you know.
Sure. Does it ever affect
your ability to shoot?
Oh.
I may waste a little more film
than I should.
But, for some reason,
with the camera, I'm not so bad.
What, uh...
What's your endgame in this?
Chisso
doesn't believe us patients.
They don't believe
we are suffering.
So we want to look
the president in the eyes.
We want him to see us and then
tell us that we don't suffer.
What makes you think
he's gonna listen to you?
I don't know.
Maybe if we make a noise
loud enough,
they won't have a choice.
With you,
we have a better chance.
Last night I rode my bicycle
all the way up to Tsunagi...
...because I heard about one family.
At first, they didn't want to let me in.
I asked them why...
they haven't been seen
in the neighbourhood lately.
I could see the shame on their faces.
It turns out their young boy
was very sick with Minamata disease.
I asked them to join us,
that we wanted help.
They considered but ultimately
their shame won out and they declined.
They love their son just as they should.
In all cases of Minamata,
there is someone to blame.
The suffering is caused by an evil...
...that we know as a fact!
So, here we are.
We have a choice.
We can let the world know.
If we are loud enough, they will listen.
Accept your responsibility!
Come on.
Is he alone?
I think so.
I hate that shit.
I used to fucking hate
gym class.
They used to make us all
sit down in a row,
cross-legged, you know?
And I couldn't do it. My legs
just don't work like that.
They don't work
like that.
And...
I know you don't understand
a word that I'm saying,
but that's not gonna stop me
from talking, so...
..you might as well
just dig in, kid.
You like jazz?
Well, you'd better, 'cause
jazz... jazz is what we've got.
It's just fucking jazz.
Improvisation. Everything.
See this?
Anyone could do this. Anyone.
Takes nothing.
You point, focus, click.
And most important... fuck up.
Fuck up because that's
the only way to learn.
So...
..you take it, kid.
I'm sick of it.
I should have known better...
coming here.
So you go on.
Play the music.
I'm, uh...
I'm not really sure if I can
hear it anymore, you know?
I don't believe you.
I mean, what kind of
photographer
gives the camera away?
Unbelievable!
Passing the torch, Aileen,
is how one dies gracefully.
Somebody said that once.
- You alright?
- What?
Yeah, Kiyoshi.
It's probably best
you know this now.
I disappoint people
and I disappoint people always.
Where are we?
Ah, Aileen found you two
a little home to stay in.
- What? Really?
- Yes.
Me and her?
Yes.
Wow. That was nice.
Come with me.
We also put together
a darkroom for you.
I set it up just the way
you have back home.
Thank you.
Pleasure.
Gene, good news.
We're moving up your piece.
I think we might have an issue
with more photographs
than car ads for the first time
for three years.
It turns out there's
a UN environmental conference
in Stockholm in a month.
Very first of its kind.
We need to coordinate the two.
Gee whiz, Bob,
I don't think I've heard you,
uh, this excited
since they faked
the moon landing.
And Millie has shaken every
tree with the anti-nuke folks
and the WHO here and in Japan.
We have all the science
to highlight your images.
Is he saving
his receipts?
So, how's it going out there?
Oh, it's... it's fun. It's fun.
I'm having a great time.
I wish you were here.
I'd... I'd... I'd let you
buy me a drink.
There's no wiggle room
on this one, Gene.
If we don't have the images
by next week, we won't make it.
You know what? What?!
- Gene...
- I got a bad connection, Bob.
- I've got a bad connection.
- Gene...
Yeah, I might have had
a little something to drink
and I didn't know
what I was doing.
I asked the people to give
whatever cameras
and film they had.
Oh!
Thank you very much.
Maybe you can join me
thanking the people.
Oh, yeah. Thank you. Thanks.
Bow.
Alright.
Thank you.
That's my camera.
Is this yours?
Yeah, that's me.
That's mine.
Great. Got it. Alright.
Well, that's alright.
How do we turn it to photos?
- What?
- How is it turn into photos?
Then you turn it
like this. Alright?
Turn it like this.
Come here, you do it.
Give me your hands.
Here. Take that. OK?
Right?
Put that hand there.
OK, now, I got you.
Now, just turn it like that.
Right?
- Like that.
- Aren't you afraid of touching me?
You're not afraid to touch me?
Why would I be?
Your hands shake because
you have Minamata disease too?
No, no. No, no. I...
No, I just drink a bunch.
What's this kid's name?
Sigeru!
Ah. Now...
Gene.
Um... it's getting late.
Maybe he should be in bed, no?
Thanks, kid.
He wants to learn how to make
the film strip
into big pictures.
Um, I'm not really here
to give photography classes.
Especially to kids.
OK, I'll teach him.
I'll teach you.
Um... you take it.
Here. You got it?
And you will take
some pictures, huh?
And we'll develop them later.
Hmm.
OK?
Thank you.
OK, pal.
- Pretty good, that kid.
- Mm-hm.
- You like that one?
- Can I have it?
No. You can't just have it. No.
Maybe I can help?
You know, uh...
..the Native Americans,
they believed that a photograph
would take a piece
of the subject's soul.
But what... what gets left out
of the fine print is...
..that it can also take a piece
of the photographer's soul.
You understand what I'm saying?
It, uh...
It will break your heart.
So, if you take it...
..you take it seriously.
Agreed?
This way.
- Put your stuff here.
- Mmm.
It's for my aunt.
Goddamn.
Phew.
I'm glad that worked.
May I? May I?
Yes.
OK, I'm gonna see if I can
find something we can use
at the shareholders meeting.
It's OK to take a picture.
Just don't show his face.
Right. Hey, listen.
People must see what's going on
behind the eyes
because that's where
the truth is.
It's an empathy thing.
- I need faces.
- Well, we need empathy here.
OK.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you very much.
OK. Let's go find the nursery.
Oh. That's... Yeah.
Uh, let's turn around now.
- Let's go.
- Go this way.
Just keep going.
Slip in here. Quick,
quick, quick, quick, quick.
Gene! Aileen!
I found the lab.
Dr Yamashita's been
the chief doctor for Chisso
since the first victims
showed up.
They had to be running tests.
They must have found something.
Hey! I found something.
It says the cat he fed
from Chisso's pipe water
reacted just like the patients.
Spasms.
Paralysis.
Convulsions.
Which is exactly what happened
when one is poisoned
with mercury.
It literally destroys
brain tissue.
And for 15 years, they knew.
They knew, Gene.
And they kept poisoning people.
Give me that.
You turn around, pick up your
camera, check your settings.
You cannot let your emotions
run the show
'cause you will fucking lose
and sometimes
you might fucking die.
Focus on the photograph
you want to take.
Focus on what you want to say.
Do it now.
You remember how it
affected you emotionally, right?
How did it make you feel?
Was it unpleasant?
A... a menace? Was it evil?
Just over here. You're changing.
Many things.
Yeah. OK.
Now...
Take it out.
Dump it in the soup.
So here's a little secret
of mine.
Use your hands a lot.
Caress the image.
You warm the print
with the body heat
from your hands.
That's how you tell your story.
OK.
Now, here. Dry your hands.
Thank you.
What for?
Oh, wait.
Ooh. Don't move.
Don't move. Don't move.
Click.
Aren't you supposed to ask
permission first?
Permission... permission is like
asking for a kiss, no.
It destroys the moment.
You just gotta take it.
Like that?
Something like that, yes. Yeah.
Just, uh...
..try not to forget
about the fine print, kid.
Hmm.
If human beings are still
the masters of creation...
we have to overthrow this poisoned world.
Is this civilisation?
Is this the so-called
period of rapid growth?
But done at the cost
of sacrificing countless lives?
Our beautiful blue ocean is now made
into a deadly sea by those people.
So, if you are a human being,
please stand up...
and fight!
Remember, we never wanted a war.
But we have to fight.
Let's make this the last battle for humanity.
Please stand up!
Go! Go!
- No, no!
- What are you doing?
Gene!
It's OK.
I'll be back.
Mr Smith. Come in.
- Thank you.
- Please sit.
Would you like something
to drink? Water?
You know, I actually think
I'd rather wait
until I get outside the building
before I drop dead,
so, um, perhaps a soda pop,
you know,
with the top still on it,
in the bottle.
OK.
Thank you.
Mr Smith, do you know what
'parts per million' means?
Without getting confused
by all the science,
it is a very, very small amount.
And small amounts are accepted.
Even in this bottle,
unopened bottle of cola...
..there may be the tiniest
amount of some material
you might not expect
or appreciate.
But it's microscopic.
Barely even there.
May I show you something?
Look over there.
The Cyclator.
We spent much money
creating a system
that keeps the water safe.
Huh. I even drank from it
to prove its safety.
It's... it's a great photograph.
It's really a nice photograph.
- Oh, thank you.
- You're welcome.
So... let's take a walk.
Do you know what we make here?
Toxic chemicals.
Good chemicals.
Chemicals that have
fertilised the land.
Help feed millions.
And chemicals needed to make
plastics, even medicines.
Also chemicals
for developing photographs.
And chemicals
that make 35mm film.
Like the kind you use yourself,
Mr Smith.
We employ over 60%
of the residents here.
If the protesters succeed,
and they put Chisso
out of business,
what happens then?
I mean,
how the fuck would I know?
I know that you are broke,
Mr Smith.
That you owe money
and that you are on brink
of getting evicted.
You are correct, sir.
You are very correct.
But I've still got my youth...
..and my girly charm, which
I think will get me through.
A father is supposed to provide
and protect his children.
Obviously, you care
more about yourself
than your own flesh and blood.
Now, you may choose to believe
the small amount
of the local fishermen
who claim that
they have somehow been harmed
by our methods.
But, I am sorry to say,
they are the parts per million,
relative to the greater amount,
the greater good.
You know, for a second there,
I thought you and I
was gonna be good pals,
but I can see now
that I was sadly mistaken
because you, sir,
are full of fucking shit.
- Please follow me.
- Certainly.
Why not?
Spanky and Alfalfa
gonna shoot me in the back?
I am a businessman.
I make deals.
Like we have done
with the locals
who have taken our payments
since the '20s.
It is even a line item
in our budget.
50,000 American dollars.
Here's the chance
to amend your sins.
And... uh...
..provide for the people
that counted on you.
You've led quite the career,
Mr Smith.
What else do you need to prove?
Ohh.
Chisso is winning back
the support of the people...
because we're influencing
student activists...
who are acting violently
against Chisso personnel.
This is not who we are.
Chisso are the ones acting violently.
We need to stay together on this
or we'll lose.
You know we'll lose!
We've offered good terms.
Chisso are promising
compensation will be quick.
We don't want
any more fighting in the town...
or shame brought to Minamata.
Chisso is behind this.
You are blind to it.
That's not true!
Is your goal to have Chisso
move somewhere else?
That's what they'll do
and where will our town be then?
This is not just about this town.
It's about big companies all over the world
invading the towns of
good, hard-working people,
and polluting their existence.
It's happened before...
and it will happen again!
Don't get so emotional!
Calm down!
Don't cause any trouble.
We understand how you feel.
We are all in the same pain.
But we all want it to end.
The signatures speak for themselves.
The people have spoken!
This is the right way
to settle the matter...
for all.
No more fighting!
May we see the book?
That's not necessary.
Have you pressed your signature
on this document?
No.
And you?
Uh-uh.
They have overwhelming
signatures of support in the book...
yet they won't show it.
Do we believe this is fair?
Let us see the book!
Show us! Show us!
That's my signature. I never pressed it!
That guy is dead. How could he have signed?
You're right. He is dead!
What's going on here?
Tell us!
You're full of lies!
Hello.
- Welcome.
- Sorry for the intrusion.
Shoes.
Oh, goddamnit!
Excuse us.
Hello.
Thank you.
Let's eat together.
Ohh.
- Mmm. Hmm.
- Hmm.
Good, right?
Huh?
Can she see?
- No.
- No?
Akiko can't see or talk.
She's congenital.
The foetuses absorb the mercury,
sparing the mother.
Hmm.
Mr. Eugene, are you married?
He has two children.
Ahhh.
Ah...
What? What?
What? What? What?
She's asking if you have
any pictures of your children.
- Of my children?
- Mm-hm.
You know, uh... no.
I'm ashamed to say that I don't.
It's bad. Hmm.
Unfortunately, he hasn't got any photos of them.
I need to help Mrs Matsumura
at the market.
OK.
Can you watch her?
What?
Akiko.
No.
No. I can't do that.
You'll be fine.
We'll be back in one hour.
I am not the most responsible...
- Stop it.
- No.
Let's go.
I'll go out for a while.
Don't get worried.
I'll give you a bath soon, Akiko.
I'm not so good
at this kind of thing, you know?
Sorry.
What, you want
to touch my beard?
There's not many beards
out here, right?
Fuzzy? Fuzzy-wuzzy?
♪ May God bless
and keep you always
♪ Let your wishes all come true
♪ May you always do for others
and let others do for you... ♪
♪ May you build a ladder to the
stars and climb on every rung
♪ And may you stay
forever young... ♪
♪ May you stay... ♪
♪ May you stay
♪ Forever young
Oh.
You're a good girl.
That way, we can't interfere.
Uh, you got company.
Ooh!
- You are Yamazaki Mitsuo, right?
- We will search the place.
What?
- Get the children inside.
- Don't get in our way.
OK, OK.
Don't take photos!
Don't resist!
You should be ashamed of yourselves.
Papa!
They're gone.
Everything is okay.
Mama!
Papa!
All I ask for
are any negatives,
any photos you've taken
while you've been here,
and that you go home
immediately.
And let what is happening here
play out here among Japanese,
in Minamata,
in the community and courts
where it belongs...
..and where you don't.
On a scale
of one to ten...
..fuck you.
Yeah.
Are you gonna eat?
Read the sign, Aileen!
I am being nourished
by my own hunger.
And maybe just
a tiny amount of whisky.
And maybe just a tiny amount
of amphetamine.
That's our little secret.
♪ Somewhere
♪ Beyond the sea
♪ Somewhere waiting for me
♪ My lover stands
on golden sands
♪ And watches the ship... ♪
Stop.
Oh!
Ahh!
Oh, Jesus.
Bring water.
- No, Gene! Gene, no!
- No, no, no!
Gene, no!
Gene! Gene, no!
No more. No! No!
That's it. No! I'm done. No!
Don't you dare follow me.
I'll ruin your fucking life.
No more. I'm done.
Yes?
You have
a collect call from Japan
by a Eugene Smith.
Will you accept the charges?
Can you ask him to call me back
in a few hours?
He's quite insistent that...
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'll accept the charges.
Hello, Bob. Bob?
It's terrible here.
Yeah, uh, listen,
there's no fucking chance.
Gene, talk to me.
OK. I'm coming home, Bob.
I'm not going to get the picture
and I can't do this shit
anymore.
And... and... and, by the way,
it's been made very clear to me
now that...
..that I am
seriously unwelcome here.
Bob? Bob, what's wrong?
I went to
the goddamn mat for you
and you ask me what's wrong?
Well, hey, I'm sorry.
I don't give a fuck
what you are!
Listen to me,
I need the pictures, Gene.
I need this story and
I need you to get me this story
like nobody else can.
No, you don't!
Big people hurt little people.
Little people get hurt
by big people.
Same thing here,
same thing there.
This picture, that picture.
They all burn up
in a fucking fire.
What does it matter?
And memory is the goddamn devil.
But the people over there,
they matter, right?
I know that because you told me.
No. You know what matters?
Money. Money for my kids.
Have you been drinking?
Course not, Bob.
I'm a professional. Jesus.
Gene, hang up. Go back to sleep.
In the morning,
it will all seem different.
You listen to me, pal.
I was recently
quite reluctantly escorted
by a couple of goons
to go and meet the top fella
at the Chisso joint.
What the fuck
are you talking about?
He offered me a whole lot
of money, Bob,
whole lot of dough,
and I got to say, I gotta say,
the dough was awful pretty.
You told him
how long and hard to go?
Yes, I did.
Yes, I did, like a dick.
And you know what,
I should have taken it.
But I'm a dick.
I'm a dick, Bob.
Just like you're a dick.
And do you know what?
Here's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna go right back there
and I'm gonna grab it.
I'm taking it.
Don't you dare!
Oh, yeah, no, listen.
I'll wire it to you.
You take back the six grand
that I owe you.
And then you send this
to my kids, OK?
Not OK, Eugene.
Not fucking OK!
You know how you always told me
how much your kids hated you?
You think a couple of grand's
gonna make a difference?
You really think
your kids are that naive?
Fuck you! I don't need
to listen to that shit!
You call me a sell-out.
Here's the irony.
I did, I did sell out
to the board,
to the boys with the abacus
in the basement.
Now I'm gambling the reputation
of the greatest magazine.
Bob, you gonna give me
a pep talk?
Because I actually
may need to vomit first.
67% ads and I'm losing.
Likely I won't even
have my integrity
to fall back on in my old age,
but I will have yours!
Dammit, Gene, I will have yours!
I'll tell you what -
if there's any left,
I will stuff it into a fucking
box and ship it to you.
I don't know how many more
issues I'll be able to publish,
but one of them is going to have
the most important photographic
essay of the last 30 years
or I will personally
fly out there
and kick
your pathetic, whingeing ass!
The kids in the office,
the special ones,
they don't look up to me.
Hey, Bob...
They look up to you,
because you matter.
And in reference
to your last comment,
blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah,
blah, blah.
Just bring me the story, OK?
Bring the story home.
Still there, Bob?
What the fuck?! What?
Shigro.
You...
You know there's a zoom
on that thing, right? Zoom.
Argh!
Ow!
Do you have a gun or an aspirin?
Or any drugs? No.
You want to take a picture?
Come here.
Some people may come and go
with the best of intentions...
but we can't count on them.
This is our fight.
Why do you think Chisso are hitting us...
harder and harder?
Why do you think they're getting
bolder and bolder?
You know why.
They can threaten us...
but we are going
to the shareholders meeting...
Excuse me. Hi. Excuse me.
I just want... Would you, um...
Would you mind
translating this for me?
Um...
Hi.
Hello. Um, I'm really no
good at public speaking.
I suppose that I'm one of those
a picture's worth a thousand
words type of guys, you know?
Anyway, that, uh...
That doesn't... doesn't matter.
I'm here to help, if I can.
But I need you to help me.
By allowing me...
..to spend some precious time
with you and your family.
So that I can help
to fight your fight.
So, I mean,
the question is this.
Who... who... is... is comfortable,
and willing...
..to share these...
..these very precious,
intimate moments...
..and to be photographed by me
with the utmost care
and respect?
Thank you.
Thank you. Ari... arigato.
What?
Is that good?
What does it mean?
Are you drunk?
No-one is ever drunk
if they can lie down on
the floor without holding on.
We're gonna
do this together.
You are murderers!
How many people are outside?
Over 500.
500?
Yes.
Get out of here.
I'm staying by you.
It's too dangerous. Get out!
Gene!
Mr. President.
We know there is verdict
that will arrive soon.
We hope that Chisso will accept
responsibility for its negligence.
We are not here for luxuries.
Just to know that we will be looked after
and able to die in peace.
If you are human,
listen to what we are saying.
I and Sadae Ogata.
I understand that you don't know who I am.
But you should.
Both of my daughters fell ill.
Both suffered more than I can imagine
anyone suffering, let alone a child.
My eldest daughter suffered
from convulsions for months.
So much pain that she couldn't cry.
She is dead now.
And my other daughter, Miyuki...
will never be able
to spend a day without care.
My husband and I cry often.
We weep because we fear
for what will happen...
when we are no longer able...
to take care of her.
Mr. President...
You've got nothing to say?
You are a human being too, right?
We are the same, and yet...
how can we be this different?
How can we?
I am sorry. I truly am.
No. What? No.
What happened to you...
What you have gone through...
brings sorrow in our hearts.
Please forgive us.
She said you treat her
with much dignity and respect.
Thank you for that.
She said you made her laugh.
What the fuck is that?
My child also has Minamata disease.
He is nine years old.
I work on the boats still...
when the fishermen allow me to...
but because of my symptoms...
they don't want me on their boats.
So, it's my wife that needs to work.
She works on the boats sometimes...
and many nights she is forced
to take care of both of us.
She can't do that forever.
Can she?
Mr. President.
We know that you will pay
for the old victims...
but you must pay the same
for the new victims as well.
It's your responsibility!
Am I wrong?
Mr. Uyishi, can I have a moment?
Gene! Are you OK?
OK. I'm OK.
Wh-what's this? What's this?
Some... someone just brought it.
What the fuck is that?
What is that?
He came when I was...
It's the negatives
from our darkroom!
I don't get it.
Where... where
did they come from?
Thank you all for coming
and speaking with me.
Your plight brings me much sadness.
But we've added up
the costs of your demands...
- However...
- We simply cannot pay.
Unfortunately... this is our final answer.
I can't take this anymore!
Kiyoshi! Kiyoshi!
They don't believe we're in pain.
Kiyoshi!
This blood is on your hands!
Are you okay?
We are ready.
Can I move Akiko's legs?
Excuse me.
Can I move Akiko's left hand?
Yes.
Akiko, I will move your hand
OK.
Very good.
Beautiful.
- I... I can't.
- Wait.
Ohh.
Oh.
Fuck it.
Hmm.
Do me a favour.
Get me the, uh...
Oh.
- ..my shutter reel. Yeah?
Thank you.
OK.
Sonofabitch.
He got it.
He fucking got it.
We have to pay.
Somehow we will find a way.
We must.
We won. We won!
Today, we have won the battle.
But the war persists.
We must continue to fight.
To fight for our children...
so their children have something...
that they can fight for.
But all of you here...
and the people who stood with us...
have taught me that this a fight
we can win!
Go home tonight
and find some happiness with your families.
Because tomorrow we have more to do.
To fight for those that cannot.
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull